metrojoint.com 2009-06-19

# Privacy Policy - MetroJoint.com

---|---  
|   
---  
|    
---  
| 

###   Privacy Policy  
  
---  
| We, at MetroJoint.com, take your privacy very seriously and abide by the following policy to ensure your satisfaction. If you have any concerns, please do not hesitate to contact us.   
---  

| •   | What information does MetroJoint.com collect/track about me?  
---|---  
•   | What does MetroJoint.com do with the information it collects/tracks?  
•   | With whom does MetroJoint.com share the information it collects/tracks?  
•   | Tell me about links with other sites.  
•   | Tell me about Cookies.  
•   | Tell me about MetroJoint.com's policy on correcting, updating or removing personal information.  
•   | Changes in MetroJoint.com's privacy policy.  
•   | Tell me about security of my personal information.  
•   | Tell me about e-mail choice/opt-out policy.  
•   | Tell me how to contact MetroJoint.com.  
  |    
| **   What information does MetroJoint.com collect/track about me? **  
---  
  
MetroJoint's sole purpose is to assist you in creating your very own social network and virtual world. Whether you are seeking friendship, a casual or a serious relationship, MetroJoint is here to help you. 

To accomplish the above purpose, our members create unique profiles (provide personal information) and our matching technology provides matches based on pre-selected criteria. 

**The public (visitors, other members, or anyone not employed by MetroJoint.com or NCrypted Technologies (technology partner) cannot use the information we gather to identify specific individuals.**

MetroJoint.com gathers two types of information. Information members submit to us and information not directly submitted by members.  
  
| **       •  Information members submit to us. **  
---  
  | 

**Public** :

We define public information (gender, age and height) as personal information that will be displayed on MetroJoint.com but cannot be used to identify a particular member. The personal information we gather may or may not include: customer-specified MetroJoint.com username, gender, age, religion, income range, occupation, preference/lifestyle information and general geographic location. 

**Private:**

We define private information as information that allows others to contact a member through means other than MetroJoint.com. It includes information about the member other than what is displayed on the site. 

This information is gathered from members and guests who apply for the various services MetroJoint.com offers. This information includes, but is not limited to: email address, first name, last name, a user-specified password, mailing address, zip code and telephone number. 

**Surveys & Contests: **

From time-to-time MetroJoint.com requests information from users via surveys or contests. Participation in these surveys or contests is completely voluntary. Information requested may include contact information (such as name and shipping address), and demographic information (such as zip code, age, etc.). 

**MetroJoint.com's Partners:**

The Partners program is a vehicle for other sites to link to the MetroJoint.com site. No personal member information is exchanged with MetroJoint partners.  
  
| **      • Information not directly submitted by members to MetroJoint.com **  
---  
  | **Aggregate:**  
  | This information -- browser type and IP address \-- is general in nature and is gathered for all users of MetroJoint.com. It cannot be and is not used to identify any individual user.   
   
| **   ** **What does MetroJoint.com do with the information it collects/tracks?**  
---  
•  | **Public:**

Public information supplied by the member is intended to be viewed by visitors to the site. This information is used by visitors for searching and matching purposes. Public information cannot be used to identify a specific member by name, address, etc.   
  
•  | **Private:**

We primarily use email addresses submitted by members to verify enrollment and when forwarding anonymous e-mails from ad responders. Respondees' email addresses are not disclosed to the responder. We also use members email addresses to send news/updates regarding our site, but the member may choose not to receive emails of this type by unsubscribing. 

Email addresses may also be used in private correspondence with members for customer service. Financial information is used to bill members for products and services. All other private information submitted by members is confidential and will not be disclosed except as required by law or to protect members of MetroJoint.com. All private information can be updated or deleted by the member at any time.  
  
•  | **Surveys & Contests:**  
Contact and other information collected for contests will be used to notify the winners and award prizes. Survey information will be used for monitoring or improving user-satisfaction.   
•  | **MetroJoint.com's Partners:**  
Information submitted by the MetroJoint partner is used for establishing and maintaining a business relationship. No personal or business information is shared outside the relationship between MetroJoint.com and the MetroJoint partner. MetroJoint partners cannot view or access private information about MetroJoint.com members.   
  
  |    
**   ** **With whom does MetroJoint.com share the information it collects/tracks?**  
  
Except where you are expressly informed otherwise or as described immediately below. 

**We do not sell, rent, share, trade or give away any of your personal information except to our technology partner -[NCrypted Technologies](http://www.ncrypted.net/).**

If you register with MetroJoint.com through one of our co-branded versions, your registration and profile information may be shared with the co-branding partner solely for the purpose of fulfilling the services provided by the co-branded site and any related promotional offers.

**We encourage you to review the privacy policy of the co-branded partner for questions about their use of your personally identifiable information and how you can modify or delete it.**  
  
** Top **  
**   ** **Tell me about links with other sites.**  
  
MetroJoint.com does provide links to other sites but is not responsible for the privacy practices of other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by MetroJoint.com 

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, please contact us   
  
** Top **  
**    Tell me about Cookies. **  
  
MetroJoint.com uses cookies to deliver various services and to keep track of your personal preferences. A cookie is a small text file that can be entered into the memory of your browser to help a site recognize repeat users, facilitate the user's ongoing access to and use of the site and allow a site to track usage behavior and compile aggregate data that allows Internet services to make content improvements and conduct targeted advertising. 

If you do not want information to be collected through cookies, use the browser's function that allows a user to deny the cookie feature. You can also delete cookie files from your computer at your discretion.

**Please note that the use of cookies is a necessary part of the MetroJoint.com technology and is necessary if you wish to access MetroJoint.com.** If you disable the cookie feature on your browser or delete cookie files from your computer, you may not be able to access certain features/services on MetroJoint.com. Cookies may also be necessary to provide you with certain features like customized look and feel, customized information, etc.

MetroJoint.com uses cookies to provide its services, to deliver content specific to your interests, to save your password so you don't have to re-enter it each time you visit different pages on our site, and for other purposes. **We do not and will not use cookies to collect private information from any user!**

Also, please note that cookies are used only to recollect information sent to your computer from MetroJoint.com. We cannot access any information not sent by MetroJoint.com.

Some of our business partners may use cookies on our site (for example, advertisers). However, we have no access to or control over these cookies.  
  
** Top **  
**   ** **Tell me about MetroJoint.com's policy on correcting, updating or removing personal information.**  
MetroJoint.com gives users several options for modifying or removing their information from our database. Please visit your "My Page" to modify/remove your information (edit profile) or contact us.  
** Top **  
**   ** **Changes in MetroJoint.com's privacy policy.**  
  
If we change our privacy policy, we will prominently post a link to those changes on our homepage so that our users are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. 

If at any point we decide to use personally identifiable information in a manner different from that stated at the time it was collected, we will notify users by way of an email.

Users will have a choice to allow/disallow MetroJoint.com the use of their information in this different manner, and we will then use information in accordance with the privacy policy under which the information was collected.  
  
** Top **  
**   Tell me about security of my personal information. **  
  
MetroJoint.com takes every precaution to protect its users' information. When users submit sensitive information via the website, the information is protected both online and offline. 

All of our users' information is restricted in our offices and data center. Only employees (for example, a customer service representative) who need the information to perform a specific job are granted access to personally identifiable information.

If you have any questions about the security at our website, please contact us.  
  
** Top **  
**   ** **Tell me about e-mail choice/opt-out policy.**  
  
Our users are given the opportunity to 'opt-out' of having information used for purposes not directly related to our site at the point where we ask for the information. 

Users who no longer wish to receive our newsletter or promotional materials from our partners may opt-out of receiving these communications by following the instructions contained in the email.   
  
** Top **  
**   ** **Tell me how to contact MetroJoint.com.**  
  
If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this website, please   
contact us.  
**   Top   **  
  
Wanna join in? Create free account
